foreign
[Music]
ER has settled into my Valley the golden
glows are blooming roses are bright and
fragrant and most importantly blueberry
farms are opening their doors to Hungry
visitors the heat of August has made me
look forward to Autumn and I cannot wait
for the cool crisp feel of October
mornings
I had to travel a ways to get to this
forum as I live in a rural area I rarely
drive on highways and it is always
interesting seeing the cars speeding
past and how there are always a handful
that Rush by and tailgate other cars in
order to get to the next stop sign just
a little bit faster even if by only a
few minutes
when I see this I can't help but wonder
what are you rushing for
is there so little to enjoy in the
present that we must hurry in order to
almost avoid it and when we get to where
we want to go will we rush through that
too for how long will we cement that
habit of going faster and faster when
will it be time to stop
[Music]
obviously these are fairly meaningless
thoughts in regards to traveling but I
like to find little reasons to
concentrate on picking blueberries and
savoring every moment from the juice on
my face to the grass underfoot I keep
this sentiment close to my heart to
remember that even harvesting on a
sweltering summer day getting all sweaty
and tired is still a gift and there's no
reason to rush
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I took several pounds of blueberries
home and decided to make a galette to
share with friends and family however I
did not have the proper pastry flour and
decided to use hard wheat flour from
whole grain Farm only a few miles away
this proved to not work out as well as
the dough was not as pliable and neat
but it was still very tasty and
healthier than the alternative so I
suppose I can't complain it's always an
event when I bake it's hard to know
what's going to happen for those who've
been watching for a long time you may
remember the exploding pie incident I
like to keep things interesting to say
the least
thank you
[Music]
with the day coming to a close I stored
the rest of my blueberries and settled
down for a cup of tea with my animal
friends and as the sun set we read some
spooky Summer Stories by candlelight and
looked forward to the coming Frost
[Music]
foreign
I'll admit I'm not in a chatty mood
today I have several people I love in my
life having a very hard time they are
quite young and they are trying to find
their place in this world and they are
struggling to do that and I know while
those challenging times are necessary
for all of us to learn and grow and
become you know who we want to be it is
still hard to hear people you love
having a hard time and so I have just
been pretty quiet today doing my best to
go slowly honor how I'm feeling and
accept if I'm not that chatty so I did
just want to say a few words of some
updates I am working again at my local
bookstore and it is such a gift I am so
excited about it I'm actually helping
them run their Instagram and I am able
to take photos and chat about books and
that has just been so much fun I think
also work talking for yourself is really
exciting and wonderful but it is a
roller coaster of ups and downs and so I
think having also a very steady job
something that gives me a very you know
set income will be helpful for peace of
mind as well it feels nice to mix up the
week with a job that is so peaceful and
even though it gets quite busy at the
bookstore it still feels usually fairly
quiet most of the time and I'm able to
just spend time Tiding and cleaning and
alphabetizing and I really enjoy it so
do look forward to at least a couple
videos about life at the bookstore
because it is a very meaningful part of
my week another thing that is on my mind
is that you can't tell but it is
actually extremely Smoky out right now
we have hit that inevitable time of
Summer where wildfires start and so it
is a quite unhealthy to be breathing
Outdoors too much it it is an
unfortunate but inevitable part of life
over here where things can get so dry
and hot looking forward to the fall
because when Autumn comes around there
comes Autumn Reigns also the frost the
coolness it is always such a wonderful
remedy for this time of year and it is
exactly what we need and so I'm sending
all of you so much love thank you so
much for your support of my Etsy shop
I'm sending these extra bookmarks with
every order and stickers with every
order now that uses the discount code
Whimsical for 10 off so I do appreciate
the support there it helps keep this
channel going it is definitely what has
made everything possible so thank you so
so much and I will see you very soon and
I will I'm sure be in a much chattier
cheerful mood but you know we all have
to honor how we feel every week
sometimes we might just be tired
sometimes we might be feeling any sort
of way and I think it's wonderful to
just except that it reminds us of our
humanity and that it's quite beautiful
to feel all these things I think I will
just sit here on my porch for just a
little while before I go back inside
with the air purifier and I will just
enjoy being here and I hope the same for
you
foreign
so I will say goodbye and I'm wishing
you the very best
see you soon
[Music]